Hello Hello Friends Welcome to your
own channel product
best wishes to my friend Good Good
Morning I am going to talk about
Equitas Buildings how will the exam
provide a micro name Housing Loans
and Michael name Friends Now this is a consumer
company
welcome to this is an existing
company whose stock is 504 in the market
Equitas Buildings has given
positive returns of 170 percent at a price of 70 per cent
and it had given dividend per share to its shareholders in the dividend
which was given on 11 Feb 27 Now let's talk about the
advantages and disadvantages of opening a quintal
first of all entry Singh
value current place left behind intrinsic
value has
performed less than video subscribe
David
Subscribe This is like
entry point out and culture lab
staff is not able to what do you believe and
not go on jhal dot over there
giving tickets to the discussion along with the website technical
advisors are covering it and seven
It is being graded along with the rounds, which is
Prasanna Trading. We will talk about
fair and comparison for a minute and
building things on the company. The market
Prakash Mathur at last Cholamandalam
Investment tried according to all, the
back is the cheapest, which means we are
getting the stock at the cheapest price. And on the other hand,
it is giving the
biggest difference compared to other oil companies.
Now let's talk about Morning
Friend's total promoter holding. In the last six
months,
the promoter has kept his horse and stunt,
which is considered very positive. There is no
voter polling promoter notification on low flame, so
this is the worker, there was an
increase of control. In the last three months,
we have liked 5 and a half, our
Jyoti is folding, which has
increased the momentum in the city, which is again considered very positive.
So now let's talk about the
chart on time holding and technical. The
technical chart is it, it had given pregnant for the new 2021,
which
can be considered in invert direct hotel, you
can consider regular channel, ascending.  You
can tie a record of triangle or you
can earn festival water formation, it
reached 14311 which also came in 2019
and its trend which is not going tight is coming out to be
151 and with that the
stop loss will be 112 and it is possible that
in the coming days
you will get to see it now let's talk about the
technical indicators of this share, how to
technical indicators first of all the
white LED in embassy,
in this program the big ones are getting
smaller but still it takes us closer, it is
above the Shivling which is considered positive,
after that we will talk that RSS is
trading at 365, this is
considered very good, I will
talk about the volume, the volume is
gradually decreasing in the share which is
showing that it may take some time for it to
achieve its target, it may happen
soon, accordingly and by now
you should do it immediately so that you can see it, we will
talk on the phone,
I have Avdhesh's line tomorrow  It is not coming but the
green is there, green is the line of the ninth and this
bride which is the line of this channel, so Payal
goes now, salary is less but
in that Payal is the symbol, its time laptop will
come up, when the blue line related to these things is
toe support
pencil, it will increase a lot, so I hope
you liked my video and if
you like my video then you should
subscribe to my channel, you should like my videos
and share it with your friends
because our Guru has
said that by sharing things increase, they do not decrease,
we do not want partners, we do
not want to spread it to anyone, we want
that whatever information remains with us, if we read this then
friends share it with everyone,
thank you.